

WEB DEVELOPER



PROFILE

My name is Nematullo, I'm 26 years old. I have experience in web development & design. Knowledge of WordPress, HTML, CSS, and igyascript.

I have more than 6 years of experience in the field of Web Designing. I've been doing website development and management in my last workplace. I have experience in building and managing corporate websites (based on WordPress CMS and HTML/CSS) for a company, where I worked and for clients.

I also have experience in SEO, SMM, Web server/hosting management, Website migration, email configuration/setup, SSL, DNS etc.



CONTACT ME



+998 93 630 2069



info@nematullo.com



PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

WordPress

HTML & CSS

JavaScrip[,]

Adobe Photoshop



GET IN TOUCH



NEMATULLO.COM



LINKEDIN.COM/IN/NEMATULLO



WORK EXPERIENCE =

SZUTEST Technology

Web Developer in Istanbul, TR September 2017 - 2022

Web Design/Development Search Engine Optimization (SEO) Graphic Design

SZUTEST

Graphic & Web Designer in Istanbul, TR October 2016 - 2022

Web Design Graphic Design

FREELANCER

Freelance Web Developer 2013 - 2016



EDUCATION =

ANDIJAN COMPUTER TECHNOLOGY COLLEGE (2010-2013)

Specialist in Information and Communication Systems ICT Specialist directed on Business

STUDY CENTER AT THE ANDIJAN STATE UNIVERSITY (2010-2012)

English Language

English Teacher and Translator

Q COURSES / CERTIFICATES =

HTML CERTIFICATE

SoloLearn 2017

CSS CERTIFICATE

SoloLearn 2018

JAVASCRIPT CERTIFICATE

SoloLearn 2020

TECHNICAL SEO CERTIFICATE

SEMrush 2021

THE ONLINE MARKETING FUNDAMENTALS

Google 2017



LANGUAGES & SKILLS ——

ENGLISH

UZBEK

O HTML/CSS

GOOGLE SHEETS

WEBSITE MANAGEMENT

RUSSIAN

O WORDPRESS O MICROSOFT OFFICE

GOOGLE TAG MANAGER

0

TURKISH

BOOTSTRAP

O YANDEX METRICA

O GOOGLE ANALYTICS

O

O SEO

SEMRUSH

O GOOGLE SEARCH CONSOLE